

Juan José Pischetz

FullStack Developer

Glad to see you here!

I'm a full-stack developer, passionate about programming, so I constantly like to learn new technologies. Furthermore, I want to develop platforms that impact people's lives, improving their quality of life. 10 years of experience in entrepreneurship led me to develop a wide range of soft skills. I'm a proactive, emphatic leader who loves to motivate team members to achieve the project's goals, I can deal with pressure and accomplish deadlines.

Professional Experience

MVP PawsFounding, HENRY (professional practice)

11/2022 - 12/2022

My role here was project manager/developer. Cause I recruited the team and laid the foundations of the product design, the objective to be met, and the first user stories. furthermore mainly worked on the frontend, highlighting geolocation as my main achievement.

Stack: TypeScript - Prisma - MongoDB React - Redux Toolkits - Tailwind CSS

https://github.com/JuanjoPischetz/PF-Henry-Grupo05 ☑

Teaching Assistant Tutor, HENRY

10/2022 - 12/2022

Bootcamp Assistant (TA) for Full-Stack Development Students.

Main tasks:

- Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration to the study group.
- Guide students in the first steps of the course.
- Assist to solve exercises and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Propose ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes.

SPA Videogames, *HENRY (professional practice)*

10/2022 - 11/2022

SPA that consumes external API to show the newest video games in retro-neon style.

STACK: PostgreSQL, Express, React, Redux, Node.js

Styling: CSS Modules

https://github.com/JuanjoPischetz/PI-VideoGames 🗷

Education

FullStack Developer (PERN Stack), HENRY

+1200 hours of coding, makes me a skillful developer at: Javascript, Node.js, Express, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, React, Redux.

Languages

Spanish

English

EF SET C2